- [Instructor] So before we start adding endpoints
to our server, let's set up our folder structure
for a project.
I personally put everything in a source folder
and then start branching out the folders
and files I'll use for the server,
my controllers, models and routes,
so let's get to it.
Inside the backend folder,
I'm going to start adding a whole bunch of folders here.
So we're going to start by adding controllers.
We're also going to add models.
And we're also going to add routes.
And inside of each of these folders,
we're going to add one file.
So in the controllers, we're going to add
a playerControllers.js file.
Inside the models we're going to add
a playerModel.js.
And then in the routes,
we're going to add soccerRoutes.js.
So this is fairly straightforward,
and we'll start adding items to this file
as we add our routes, models, and controllers.
So let's move on.